const ProbabilityQuestions = [
    {
        question: "What is the probability of rolling a 4 on a fair six-sided die?",
        options: ["1/6", "1/4", "1/2"],
        correct_option: "1/6"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the probability of drawing an Ace from a standard deck of 52 playing cards?",
        options: ["1/13", "1/4", "1/52"],
        correct_option: "1/13"
    },
    {
        question: "If you flip a coin twice, what is the probability of getting two heads?",
        options: ["1/2", "1/4", "1/3"],
        correct_option: "1/4"
    },
    {
        question: "A bag contains 3 red, 5 blue, and 2 green marbles. What is the probability of drawing a blue marble?",
        options: ["1/2", "1/5", "5/10"],
        correct_option: "1/2"
    },
    {
        question: "If you flip a coin three times, what is the probability of getting exactly one head?",
        options: ["3/8", "1/8", "1/2"],
        correct_option: "3/8"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the probability of drawing a heart from a standard deck of cards?",
        options: ["1/4", "1/2", "1/8"],
        correct_option: "1/4"
    },
    {
        question: "If a single card is drawn from a standard deck of 52 cards, what is the probability of drawing a face card (Jack, Queen, or King)?",
        options: ["3/13", "1/13", "1/4"],
        correct_option: "3/13"
    },
    {
        question: "A bag contains 4 red, 3 blue, and 2 yellow balls. What is the probability of drawing a yellow ball?",
        options: ["2/9", "1/3", "1/9"],
        correct_option: "2/9"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the probability of drawing a 7 or an 8 from a standard deck of 52 cards?",
        options: ["2/13", "1/13", "1/26"],
        correct_option: "2/13"
    },
    {
        question: "If you roll two six-sided dice, what is the probability that the sum of the numbers rolled is 7?",
        options: ["1/6", "1/12", "1/36"],
        correct_option: "1/6"
    }
];

export default ProbabilityQuestions;
